<items>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.1060research.com/
        </link>
        <image>1060.png
        </image>
        <title>1060 NetKernel</title>
        <description>
            A virtual Internet OS with an XML runtime. It offers a microkernel modular component architecture and
            integrates a comprehensive set of XML technologies. It features an XML runtime, XML pipeline processes with
            loops and exception handling, virtualized modular URI address spaces, and a dependency-based cache."
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.abaxx.com/elements
        </link>
        <image>abaXX.gif
        </image>
        <title>abaXX</title>
        <description>
            abaXX elements is a full-fledged portal-building software including easy-to-use MVC support, a Portlet
            framework, an event model, a Portlet deployment model, a Struts compatibility option, a tag library, a set
            of web widgets (trees etc.), a ready-to-run 'vanilla' base portal, a rather amazing live web portal
            configurator ('PortalBuilder'), and plenty of professional documentation. The developer licence is free.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://blogs.opensymphony.com/plightbo/2006/08/item_able_a_complete_java_w.html</link>
        <title>Able</title>
        <description>
            item Able is a full Java-based web development stack designed to make web development painless. In a
            sense, it is an attempt to bring together quality opensource tools in one cohesive stack, similar to what
            Rails has done for Ruby, while also encouraging common practices I've used in software engineering for a
            long time.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://activemq.apache.org/
        </link>
        <image>activemq.png
        </image>
        <title>ActiveMQ</title>
        <description>
            Apache ActiveMQ is the most popular and powerful open source Message Broker and Enterprise Integration
            Patterns provider.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.adeptiabpm.com/
        </link>
        <image>adeptia.gif
        </image>
        <title>Adeptia</title>
        <description>
            Adeptia provides Business Process Management (BPM) and SOA-based integration technology to easily and
            quickly automate business processes and data flows using industry-specific standards.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://aejaks.sourceforge.net/Aejaks_Home/index.html
        </link>
        <image>aejaks-logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Æjaks</title>
        <description>
            Æjaks combines the server-side Ajax windowing system Echo2 with the powerful simplicity of the Tcl langauge.
            The result is a rich development environment in which to develop Ajax-based web applications, often with
            much less code to write.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://apriority.dyndns.biz/aesplash.html
        </link>
        <image>AgilEntityLogo.png
        </image>
        <title>AgilEntity</title>
        <description>
            AgilEntity is a clustered java based framework that provides a platform for building extremely robust
            distributed applications that are all managed using the Action Oriented Workflow paradigm.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.alibaba-inc.jp/
        </link>
        <image>alibaba_jp.gif
        </image>
        <title>Alibaba Japan</title>
        <description>
            Alibaba Japan uses Jetty as a dynamic gateway to translate https://www.alibaba.com into the Japanese
            language.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://wiki.alfresco.com/wiki/Managing_Alfresco_Lifecyle_with_Maven
        </link>
        <image>alfresco-dev-logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>Alfresco</title>
        <description>
            This m2 archetype provides (with zero conf remote creation hosted in SourceSense mvn repositories) the
            following features amongst others: property filtering,rapid prototyping, releasing, documentation site, LDAP
            configuration samples, jetty embedded run, ant support.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.jfrog.org/sites/artifactory/latest/index.html
        </link>
        <image>artifactory.png
        </image>
        <title>Artifactory</title>
        <description>
            Artifactory is a Maven2 proxy repository with advanced features. It is based on JCR (using JackRabbit as the
            implementation), with a web UI based on Wicket, and embeded Jetty for quick start. All artifacts are stored
            in an embedded Derby DB.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://atomic.catchpole.net/
        </link>
        <image>atomicobjects.gif
        </image>
        <title>Atomic</title>
        <description>
            Atomic is an object environment that creates a virtual space in which Java objects can be created, linked
            and taught to relate to one another. Atomic uses technology found in neutral networks, databases and
            distributed systems. Atomic can be used as a stand-alone server, with integrated web, console and 3D GUI
            services. It can also be used as library within other products.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.bdm-systems.com/en/products.htm
        </link>
        <image>bluecube.png
        </image>
        <title>bluecube</title>
        <description>
            bluecube is the powerful business intelligence (bi) solution by bdm business data management. It includes
            it’s own ETL and OLAP engine, connectors with predefined content, a very mighty cube builder and a
            convinient MS Excel client.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://openbluedragon.org/
        </link>
        <image>bluedragon.png
        </image>
        <title>Open BlueDragon</title>
        <description>
            Open BlueDragon, was released as a GPLv3 open source item, on the 3rd of May 2008. Designed to capitalise
            on the popularity of the Java CFML runtime engine, by bringing together a community of users and experts to
            drive the future of CFML as a whole.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.blue-elephant-systems.com
        </link>
        <image>bes.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Blue Elephant Systems</title>
        <description>
            MIDAS Configurator is a web-based configuration and administration GUI for various network and system
            management suites, eg. for HP OpenView Operations for UNIX. MIDAS allows you to browse and change the
            complete configuration data by linking all related information together. Configuration items can be saved
            transparently in a version control system. MIDAS is based on an enterprise service bus (esb) and runs on
            HP-UX, Solaris, Linux and Windows Server operating systems.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://edocs.bea.com/wlibc/docs70/index.html
        </link>
        <image>bea.gif
        </image>
        <title>WebLogic Business Connect</title>
        <description>
            Business Connect, the lightweight trading partner software for BEA WebLogic Integration, enables businesses
            to connect supply chains with demand chains, down to the smallest partners and suppliers.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://bombermine.com/
        </link>
        <image>bombermine.png
        </image>
        <title>BomberMine</title>
        <description>
            Bombermine game server is built upon jetty websocket handler.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://brainking.com
        </link>
        <image>brainking.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Brain King</title>
        <description>
            An online game server that plays chess, checkers, five in line reversi and other will-known games.
            Get a BrainKing rateing calculated by your results.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.crunchysoftware.com/browsertunnel.htm
        </link>
        <image>browsertunnel.gif
        </image>
        <title>BrowserTunnel</title>
        <description>
            BrowserTunnel allows you to perform simple control of a remote PC via a standard web browser.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://sourceforge.net/items/bugkilla
        </link>
        <image>bugkilla.gif
        </image>
        <title>BugKilla</title>
        <description>
            Bugkilla is a set of java tools for the functional test of J2EE Web Applications. Specification and
            execution of tests is automated for web front end and business logic layer. One goal of the item is to
            integrate with existing open source frameworks and tools. Jetty is used in its proxy configuration to
            capture http-communication as test procedures for the replay based tests.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.bug-track.com/
        </link>
        <image>BugTrackLogo.gif
        </image>
        <title>Bug Track</title>
        <description>
            For all development teams, who want the best Issue Tracking System, Bug-Track.com is a web based tracking
            software that is highly customizable and easy to use. Unlike Open Source and Free software, our product is
            easy to install and customize. Come in and try our free demo.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://jakarta.apache.org/cactus/index.html
        </link>
        <image>cactus.gif
        </image>
        <title>Cactus</title>
        <description>
            Cactus is a simple test framework for unit testing server-side java code (Servlets, EJBs, Tag Libs, Filters,
            ...). The intent of Cactus is to lower the cost of writing tests for server-side code. It uses JUnit and
            extends it. Cactus implements an in-container strategy.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://camel.apache.org/
        </link>
        <image>camel.png
        </image>
        <title>Apache Camel</title>
        <description>
            Apache Camel is a powerful open source integration framework based on known Enterprise Integration Patterns
            with powerful Bean Integration. Camel lets you create the Enterprise Integration Patterns to implement
            routing and mediation rules in either a Java based Domain Specific Language (or Fluent API), via Spring
            based Xml Configuration files or via the Scala DSL. This means you get smart completion of routing rules in
            your IDE whether in your Java, Scala or XML editor.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://code.google.com/p/castcluster/
        </link>
        <image>castcluster.png
        </image>
        <title>CastCluster</title>
        <description>
            CastCluster is an evolving item that aims to provide access to additional content on iTunes, Apple TV,
            iPod or Random Podcast Viewer. The current sources of content are YouTube, Google Video, Revver, local disk
            and RSS feeds.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.celerity-crm.nl/
        </link>
        <image>celerity.png
        </image>
        <title>Celerity CRM</title>
        <description>
            (Site in Dutch) Celerity CRM is an easy to use online relationship manager with different modules. The price
            is based on a low monthly per user.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.chess.com/
        </link>
        <image>chesscom.png
        </image>
        <title>Chess.com</title>
        <description>
            Chess.com is the newest and fastest growing online chess community where members can play chess, learn, and
            connect. Chess.com uses Jetty to power the next generation of live online chess servers.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.powersource.com.au/cine-intro.html
        </link>
        <image>cine-jetty-image.gif
        </image>
        <title><![CDATA[Cin&eacute;math&egrave;que]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[Cin&eacute;math&egrave;que is a comprehensive, integrated management and control solution for interactive
            video on-demand in wide area residential, residential multi-dwelling, and hospitality environments.]]>
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.cipango.org/
        </link>
        <image>cipango.png
        </image>
        <title>Cipango</title>
        <description>
            Cipango is a SIP Servlets extension to the popular Jetty HTTP Servlet engine. Cipango/Jetty is then a
            convergent SIP/HTTP Application Server compliant with both SIP Servlets 1.1 and HTTP Servlets 2.5 standards.
            It also features a Diameter extension to develop IMS applications.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://circumflex.ru/items/web/index.html
        </link>
        <image>circumflex.png
        </image>
        <title>Circumflex</title>
        <description>
            Circumflex Web Framework is a minimalistic DSL for quick and robust Web application development using Scala
            programming language https://scala-lang.org.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.cisco.com/en/US/products/hw/routers/ps314/products_data_sheet09186a0080091f30.html
        </link>
        <image>cisco.gif
        </image>
        <title>Cisco Subscriber Edge Services Manager</title>
        <description>
            CNS SESM allows service providers and mobile operators to create branded web portals. These portals can be
            used to promote value-added services, create customer loyalty, build a brand experience, differentiate
            service offers, and increase customer satisfaction
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://cocoon.apache.org
        </link>
        <image>cocoon.gif
        </image>
        <title>Cocoon</title>
        <description>
            Apache Cocoon is a web development framework built around the concepts of separation of concerns and
            component-based web development. Cocoon implements these concepts around the notion of 'component
            pipelines', each component on the pipeline specializing on a particular operation. This makes it possible to
            use a Lego(tm)-like approach in building web solutions, hooking together components into pipelines without
            any required programming. Cocoon is "web glue for your web application development needs". It is a glue that
            keeps concerns separate and allows parallel evolution of all aspects of a web application, improving
            development pace and reducing the chance of conflicts.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.collectionspace.org/
        </link>
        <image>collectionspace.png
        </image>
        <title>CollectionSpace</title>
        <description>
            CollectionSpace is an open-source collections management application that meets the needs of museums,
            historical societies, and other collection-holding organizations. CollectionSpace is designed to be
            configurable to each organization’s needs, serving as a gateway to digital and physical assets across an
            institution. The software is freely distributed via open-source licensing, and an active developer community
            ensures that CollectionSpace is continually improving.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.collettadicastelbianco.com
        </link>
        <image>colletta.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Colletta di Castelbianco</title>
        <description>
            Jetty is used to power the website of this telecommuters village in the
            mountains behind the italian riviera. The site gives information about
            the ancient stone village, it surroundings and provides a booking site
            for short and long term accomodation.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.codestreet.com/
        </link>
        <image>codestreet.jpg
        </image>
        <title>CodeStreet</title>
        <description>
            ReplayService for JMS adds a third QoS to TIBCO EMS: historical. By storing and indexing message streams in
            a high-performance data store, subsequent retrieval, search and statistics become a breeze. The Replay API
            is an implementation of JMS 1.1 with replay additions such as 'rewindable destinations'.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.proiv.com/p4web/home/products/concertocd/index.xsp
        </link>
        <image>concerto.gif
        </image>
        <title>Concerto Universal</title>
        <description>
            Concerto provides a highly efficient and portable integrated Server side JavaScript development and
            deployment environment which has a rich object model enabling rapid development of Web Applications. The
            environment provides an application framework and is fully extensible via Java objects.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.sterlingcommerce.com
        </link>
        <image>stercomm.gif
        </image>
        <title>Connect:Enterprise</title>
        <description>
            A many-to-many secure file transfer solution for large B2B initiatives. It stores both incoming and outgoing
            files in a secure data repository, and forwards them on demand. Connect:Enterprise supports multiple
            communication protocols, both legacy and Internet, and provides robust protection from external threats.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://maven.apache.org/continuum
        </link>
        <image>continuum_logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Continuum</title>
        <description>
            Continuum is a continous integration server for building Java based items. It supports a wide range of
            items: maven1, maven2, ant and shell scripts.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.phonetransact.com/
        </link>
        <image>phonetransact.png
        </image>
        <title>Credit Card Merchant Pro</title>
        <description>
            Credit Card Merchant Pro is an iPhone credit card processing application. The credit card terminal
            notification server is powered by Jetty.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.drishti-soft.com/solutions/dacx_dialer.htm
        </link>
        <image>dacx.png
        </image>
        <title>DACX Dialer</title>
        <description>
            DACX Dialer is a full-featured and scalable dialing solution, to provide totally hassle free dialing at
            reasonable hardware investment to call centers. DACX Dialer works with various technologies including SIP,
            ISDN, IAX and incorporates features like multi-campaign support, predictive dialing, lead-churning,
            extensive reporting, pluggable CRM support etc., which help our customers greatly enhance the productivity
            of their agents. DACX predictive dialer uses an embedded Jetty server.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://cocoondev.org/daisy
        </link>
        <image>daisy_brown.png
        </image>
        <title>Daisy</title>
        <description>
            Daisy is a comprehensive content management application framework, consisting of a standalone repository
            server accessible through HTTP/XML and a high-level (remote) Java API, and an extensive Daisy browsing and
            editing DaisyWiki application. Daisy is licensed under the commercially-friendly Apache License 2.0.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://davenport.sourceforge.net/
        </link>
        <image>davenport.gif
        </image>
        <title>Davenport</title>
        <description>
            Davenport is a servlet which provides a WebDAV gateway to SMB shared resources. Typical usage would be to
            provide
            web-based read and write access to Windows shared drives. WebDAV clients, such as Windows' "Web Folders" can
            copy
            files to and from the shares over HTTP. Non-WebDAV-capable web browsers can also access the network,
            downloading
            files from shared folders in a seamless fashion. Users access shared resources using their Windows domain
            usertitle
            and password, so no account configuration is typically needed. When run over HTTPS, Davenport provides a
            secure
            means of accessing internal shared drives over the internet without requiring a VPN.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.dbsight.net/</link>
        <title>DBSight</title>
        <description>
            DBSight aids the creation of a Lucene search index from databases with an administrative interface that
            provides the
            ability to tweak search rankings by attributes of the data. Results are formatted via customizable Velocity
            templates. Because DBSight communicates directly with a database, it works with Java as well as non-Java
            frameworks.
            It has incremental-indexing, scheduler, and you can adjust your business needs. You can create a full-text
            database
            search service, and return results as HTML/XML/JSON. It uses Lucene directly in Java, but can be easily used
            with
            Ruby, PHP, or any existing database web application. Instead of worrying about Java-specific details, you
            can think
            about how users search the data, how to tweak the ranking by attributes, such as product price, or bug
            priority. You
            can easily index, re-index, incremental-index your data. And you can change the search very quickly and
            cost-effectively. Here is a screencast demo showing how to generate a text search index for an existing
            database
            application, Creating a Lucene Database Search Index in 3 Minutes
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.dieselpoint.com
        </link>
        <image>dieselpoint.gif
        </image>
        <title>Dieselpoint Search</title>
        <description>
            Dieselpoint Search (tm) is a full-featured search and navigation engine. Customers are currently
            using it to search XML, documents, databases, catalogs, intranets, and OEM applications.
            Supports 40 languages. Especially well-suited for searching XML.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.docsdb.com
        </link>
        <image>docsdb.gif
        </image>
        <title>DocsDB</title>
        <description>
            DocsDB/4 is the first document breakthrough since the invention of the
            filing cabinet. It offers truly relational document management and workflow
            through a web-based interface. Just like relational databases did two
            decades ago, relational document management will lift the restrictions of
            hierarchical structures like files and folders. DocsDB delivers flexible,
            fast and robust storage, retrieval, routing, filing, archiving and purging
            of large amounts of documents, whether on paper or electronic.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.sybase.com/products/development/easerver
        </link>
        <image>sybase-logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>EAServer</title>
        <description>
            Sybase EAServer offers enterprise-class reliability, performance and manageability in a flexible and
            standards-based
            environment. Leveraging a new modular architecture, EAServer supports custom deployments so that
            applications use
            only the server pieces that are required. The leading solution for distributed and web-enabled PowerBuilder
            applications, EAServer allows existing applications to participate in J2EE 1.4 and Service-Oriented
            Architectures
            (SOA).
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.ebineutrino.org/
        </link>
        <image>ebi.gif
        </image>
        <title>EBI Neutrino</title>
        <description>
            EBI Neutrino ERP / CRM EBI Neutrino is a Framework for Enterprise Resource Planing (ERP) and Customer
            Relation
            Mangement(CRM) software solution that combines power of distribution, inventory, E-Commerce, accounting and
            workflow.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.eclipse.org
        </link>
        <image>eclipse.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Eclipse</title>
        <description>
            Eclipse[TM] is an open source community whose items are focused on building an open development platform
            comprised of extensible frameworks, tools and runtimes for building, deploying and managing software across
            the
            lifecycle.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.alphaworks.ibm.com/tech/eclifox?open&amp;S_TACT=105AGX01&amp;S_CMP=LP
        </link>
        <image>eclifox.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Eclifox</title>
        <description>
            Eclifox is an Eclipse plug-in from IBM AlpahWorks that enables Gecko-based browsers, like Firefox, access to
            the
            Eclipse IDE.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.editme.com
        </link>
        <image>editme.jpg
        </image>
        <title>EditMe</title>
        <description>
            The hosted web site solution for wikis, blogs, content, and collaboration sites.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.encours.org/
        </link>
        <image>encours.png
        </image>
        <title>Encours</title>
        <description>
            Encours is a real-time interactive presentation system. The presentation slides are shared online. One or
            more
            lecturers control the slides and they can change the pages, and they are given a "laser" pointer to
            highlight their
            point. The audience can see the lecturer actions in real time and can ask questions to the lecturer if they
            wish.
            The lecturer can give slide control to specific audience members if necessary.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.eclipse.org/equinox/
        </link>
        <image>eclipse.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Equinox</title>
        <description>
            From a code point of view, Equinox is an implementation of the OSGi R4 core framework specification, a set
            of
            bundles that implement various optional OSGi services and other infrastructure for running OSGi-based
            systems.
            More generally, the goal of the Equinox item is to be a first class OSGi community and foster the vision
            of
            Eclipse as a landscape of bundles. As part of this, it is responsible for developing and delivering the OSGi
            framework implementation used for all of Eclipse.
            Equinox provides org.eclipse.equinox.http.jetty, an implementation of the OSGi HttpService using Jetty as
            the
            underlying engine.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.eucalyptus.com/
        </link>
        <image>eucalyptus.png
        </image>
        <title>Eucalyptus</title>
        <description>
            Eucalyptus Systems provides IT organizations in enterprises, government agencies and Web and mobile
            businesses with
            the most widely deployed cloud software platform for on-premise Infrastructure-as-a-Service (IaaS).
            Eucalyptus is
            specifically designed for enterprise cloud use, and the software platform is uniquely suited for private
            cloud or
            hybrid cloud computing. Built as an open source cloud product, Eucalyptus supports the industry-standard
            Amazon Web
            Services (AWS) cloud APIs, as well as all major virtualization platforms including Xen, KVM and VMware
            vSphere, ESX
            and ESXi.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://evrythng.com/
        </link>
        <image>evrythng.png
        </image>
        <title>EVRYTHNG</title>
        <description>
            The EVRYTHNG Engine provides high scale, industrial technology to create and serve millions of Active
            Digital
            Identities&#8482; for a company's products and other objects. These unique online profiles create a
            persistent,
            unique digital presence for any physical object on the Web. Think of a Facebook for Things&#8482; where
            individual
            objects, just like people on social networks, have their own unique digital profiles that enable
            communications,
            apps and services.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://exist-db.org
        </link>
        <image>exist.gif
        </image>
        <title>Exist DB</title>
        <description>
            eXist is an Open Source native XML database featuring efficient, index-based XPath query processing,
            extensions for
            keyword search and tight integration with existing XML development tools.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://fabulously40.com/
        </link>
        <image>fab40.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Fabulously40</title>
        <description>
            The social network for women in their 40's and up.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://felix.apache.org/site/index.html
        </link>
        <image>apache-felix-small.png
        </image>
        <title>Apache Felix</title>
        <description>
            Felix is a community effort to implement the OSGi R4 Service Platform, which includes the OSGi framework and
            standard services, as well as providing and supporting other interesting OSGi-related technologies. The
            ultimate
            goal is to provide a completely compliant implementation of the OSGi framework and standard services and to
            support
            a community around this technology. Felix currently implements a large portion of the OSGi release 4
            specification,
            but additional work is necessary for full compliance. Despite this fact, the OSGi framework functionality
            provided
            by Felix is very stable.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.fiorano.com/products/fmq/overview.htm
        </link>
        <image>fmq5_logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>FioranoMQ</title>
        <description>
            FioranoMQ 6 is the most scalable, secure, and fastest Java Messaging Server for organizations building a new
            breed
            of massively scalable, high-performance and reliable, distributed computing solutions.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.cenqua.com/fisheye
        </link>
        <image>fisheye_logo_small.gif
        </image>
        <title>FishEye</title>
        <description>
            Your source code repository contains an abundance of valuable information. This is not always easy to
            extract,
            comprehend and keep up to date. FishEye painlessly opens up your repository and helps you get the
            perspective you
            need to better understand the changes you are making to your source.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.flexraid.com/
        </link>
        <image>FlexRAID-Logo.png
        </image>
        <title>FlexRAID</title>
        <description>
            FlexRAID products are flexible and innovative and allow users to unify &amp; organize their data. Protection
            &amp;
            recovery
            from disk failures! Whether one chooses Transparent RAID &#0153; or RAID over File System, FlexRAID products
            allow
            users to transform a common PC with an existing operating system into a protected Network Attached Storage
            (NAS)
            appliance or a Hybrid Storage System (HSS), which is accessed both locally and remotely. All FlexRAID
            products are
            non-intrusive in that one can uninstall the software at any time and regain complete control of his/her
            disks and
            data without ever needing to do a data migration.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.funnelback.com/
        </link>
        <image>funnelback.png
        </image>
        <title>Funnelback</title>
        <description>
            Funnelback Internet &amp; enterprise search has the capability to search entire enterprises including
            websites,
            shared
            drives, business applications and databases. It also has advanced access controls, and can be deployed as a
            Software
            as a Service search solution, or behind the firewall on in-house servers.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.logicblaze.com
        </link>
        <image>logo_fuse.gif
        </image>
        <title>Fuse</title>
        <description>
            LogicBlaze FUSE is the SOA runtime platform provided as an open source distribution. Combining leading
            technologies
            for enterprise messaging and services in an integrated, manageable framework, LogicBlaze FUSE delivers a
            comprehensive solution for SOA runtime with reliability, scalability, high performance, and connectivity.
            The entire
            platform is provided in an accessible, open source solution, with enterprise-caliber support and services
            available.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://geonetwork-opensource.org/
        </link>
        <image>geonetwork.jpg
        </image>
        <title>GeoNetwork</title>
        <description>
            GeoNetwork opensource is a standards based, Free and Open Source catalog application to manage spatially
            referenced
            resources through the web. It provides powerful metadata editing and search functions as well as an embedded
            interactive web map viewer.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://docs.codehaus.org/display/GEOS/Home
        </link>
        <image>geoserver.gif
        </image>
        <title>GeoServer</title>
        <description>
            GeoServer is an Open Source server that connects your information to the Geospatial Web. With GeoServer you
            can
            publish and edit data using open standards. Your information is made available in a large variety of formats
            as
            maps/images or actual geospatial data. GeoServer's transactional capabilities offer robust support for
            shared
            editing. GeoServer's focus is ease of use and support for standards, in order to serve as 'glue' for the
            geospatial
            web, connecting from legacy databases to many diverse clients.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://geronimo.apache.org
        </link>
        <image>geronimo-logo.png
        </image>
        <title>Apache Geronimo</title>
        <description>
            Apache Geronimo is a new effort coordinated by the Apache Software Foundation to make a J2EE certified
            container.
            Jetty is being used as the default web container.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.gigaspaces.com/
        </link>
        <image>gigaspaces.gif
        </image>
        <title>GigaSpaces</title>
        <description>
            Nearly every application today has a web interface. XAP 6.6 embeds the Jetty servlet container, which means
            you
            enjoy XAP's performance, scalability, and resiliency even for your existing web applications.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.gngsms.net/
        </link>
        <image>gngsms.png
        </image>
        <title>Give N' Go</title>
        <description>
            GnGSmS aims to simplify the creation of dynamic SMS applications, rapid development of these application is
            the
            ultimate goal. With the scenario builder, SMS based scenarios can be created and activated immediately, No
            programming skills is required! With Simple knowledge of SQL, you can build database driven SMS
            applications.
            Although GnGSmS was created with the end user in mind, but as a programmer I was always keen to make it
            simple and
            straightforward to extend.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://code.google.com/appengine/
        </link>
        <image>appengine.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Google AppEngine</title>
        <description>
            Run your web apps on Google's infrastructure.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://code.google.com/webtoolkit/
        </link>
        <image>gwt.png
        </image>
        <title>Google Web Toolkit (GWT)</title>
        <description>
            Writing web apps today is a tedious and error-prone process. Developers can spend 90% of their time working
            around
            browser quirks. In addition, building, reusing, and maintaining large JavaScript code bases and AJAX
            components can
            be difficult and fragile. Google Web Toolkit (GWT) eases this burden by allowing developers to quickly build
            and
            maintain complex yet highly performant JavaScript front-end applications in the Java programming language.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://code.google.com/p/google-refine/
        </link>
        <image>google-refine.png
        </image>
        <title>Google Refine</title>
        <description>
            Google Refine is a power tool for working with messy data, cleaning it up, transforming it from one format
            into
            another, extending it with web services, and linking it to databases like Freebase.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://grails.org/
        </link>
        <image>grails_logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Grails</title>
        <description>
            Grails aims to bring the "coding by convention" paradigm to Groovy . It's an open-source web application
            framework
            that leverages the Groovy language and complements Java Web development. You can use Grails as a standalone
            development environment that hides all configuration details or integrate your Java business logic. Grails
            aims to
            make development as simple as possible and hence should appeal to a wide range of developers not just those
            from the
            Java community.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://lucene.apache.org/hadoop/about.html
        </link>
        <image>hadoop-logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Hadoop</title>
        <description>
            Hadoop is a framework for running applications on large clusters of commodity hardware. The Hadoop framework
            transparently provides applications both reliability and data motion. Hadoop implements a computational
            paradigm
            titled map/reduce, where the application is divided into many small fragments of work, each of which may be
            executed
            or reexecuted on any node in the cluster. In addition, it provides a distributed file system that stores
            data on the
            compute nodes, providing very high aggregate bandwidth across the cluster. Both map/reduce and the
            distributed file
            system are designed so that node failures are automatically handled by the framework.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.globalgraphics.com/software/harlequin_rip/jdf_rip.html
        </link>
        <image>harlequin.gif
        </image>
        <title>Harlequin</title>
        <description>
            The JDF Enabler for Global Graphic's Harlequin RIPs (Eclipse Release) features an
            intuitive Web-based GUI that allows multiple users to check on the status
            of JDF (Job Definition Format) jobs and view progress, along with administrator level access to
            set up HTTP JMF channels and hotfolders. The Web-based GUI and HTTP-based JMF
            job submission are implemented with a Jetty HTTP server, embedded within the JDF
            Enabler application.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://helma.org/
        </link>
        <image>helmalogo.gif
        </image>
        <title>Helma</title>
        <description>
            Helma (also called Helma object publisher, or Hop for short) is a scriptable open source web application
            server
            written in Java.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.heroku.com/
        </link>
        <image>heroku.png
        </image>
        <title>Heroku</title>
        <description>
            Run any web or background process with any web framework or worker type. Get direct, granular control over
            your
            app's workloads. Scale distributed processes effortlessly with a single command. Easily scale to millions of
            users.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://historio.us/
        </link>
        <image>historious.png
        </image>
        <title>Historious</title>
        <description>
            Have you ever read an interesting article online and then wanted to come back to it days later but couldn't
            find it
            any more? Bookmarks are not very effective because the sheer number and variety of websites we visit makes
            bookmarking a logistic nightmare.historious is here to help with that exact situation. It is basically a
            search
            engine for sites you like. Add (we call it "historify") a site using our bookmarklet (it works with all
            browsers,
            even your phone's!), our browser extensions or manually, then come back to the site and search your
            historified
            sites just by entering some keywords!
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://hiveboard.sourceforge.net/website/web/index.html</link>
        <title>HiveBoard</title>
        <description>
            HiveBoard is online shared whiteboard conferencing system. HiveBoard is developed in Java and is open
            source. It has
            a server application based on Jetty Servlet Container (in embedded mode) and a rich client application that
            connects
            to the server and can access shared whiteboards. The use of Jetty embedded server has enabled a quick (5')
            and easy
            setup of the HiveBoard server.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://devresource.hp.com/drc/topics/OVI.jsp
        </link>
        <image>hp_logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>HP OpenView Interconnect Tools</title>
        <description>
            HP OpenView Interconnect Tools for Developers (OVI) provides an easy-to-use, consistent, and stable gateway
            for
            integrating with HP OpenView applications. Because OVI is based on industry-standard technologies like Java,
            XML,
            HTTP, SOAP, JMS, and TCP sockets, it enables OpenView data to be obtained in a simplified,
            platform-independent
            fashion. All data is exchanged in standard XML document format. OVI gives systems integrators, enterprise
            application integrators, and independent software vendors a single, consistent way to exchange data with HP
            OpenView. OVI can be downloaded from https://devresource.hp.com/drc/topics/OVI.jsp
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://support.openview.hp.com/self_healing.jsp
        </link>
        <image>hp_logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>HP Openview Self-Healing</title>
        <description>
            HP OpenView Self-Healing Services automates the support process by monitoring and reporting on HP’s
            management suite
            across the customer/HP connection in order
            to assist both the customer and HP with problem diagnosis.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.hydroleaf.com
        </link>
        <image>hydroleaf.gif
        </image>
        <title>Hydroleaf</title>
        <description>
            Hydroleaf.com is a hydroponics resource for professional &amp; recreational growers / gardeners, retailing
            hydroponic kits &amp; systems, grow lights, nutrients &amp; all equipment and expertise required for indoor
            gardens
            and hydroponic greenhouses.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.hybridserverpages.com/
        </link>
        <image>HJLogo.gif
        </image>
        <title>HybridServerPages</title>
        <description>
            HybridJava is a Java™ -based component-oriented MVC technology for programming dynamic web content.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.i2p2.de/index.html
        </link>
        <image>i2plogo.png
        </image>
        <title>I2P</title>
        <description>
            I2P is an anonymizing network, offering a simple layer that identity-sensitive applications can use to
            securely
            communicate. All data is wrapped with several layers of encryption, and the network is both distributed and
            dynamic,
            with no trusted parties.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://iberagents.ib-ia.com/
        </link>
        <image>iberagents.png
        </image>
        <title>IberAgents</title>
        <description>
            The IberAgents platform is an open-source framework for component development in Java.
            It has facilities for distributed computing using web services, persistence to database and files, and
            interaction via the Web; thus providing an end-to-end solution for data management. IberAgents
            uses Jetty as its internal servlet engine for its ability to be embedded fully configured in code.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.icefaces.org
        </link>
        <image>icefaces-logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>ICEFaces</title>
        <description>
            ICEfaces is an integrated Ajax application framework that enables Java EE application developers to easily
            create
            and deploy thin-client rich Internet applications (RIA) in pure Java. ICEfaces is a fully featured product
            that
            enterprise developers can use to develop new or existing Java EE applications at no cost.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.ign.com/
        </link>
        <image>ignlogo.gif
        </image>
        <title>IGN</title>
        <description>
            IGN Entertainment (Nasdaq: IGNX), through its flagship network IGN.com, is the Internet's leading
            information and
            entertainment destination for
            teen and young adult gamers. IGN has established a leadership position delivering quality content and
            services to
            gaming enthusiasts and
            providing business customers with access to this valuable audience.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.dynix.com/products/hip/
        </link>
        <image>dynix.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Horizon Information Portal</title>
        <description>
            Horizon Information Portal, the new standard in user access, will satisfy the demands and exceed the
            expectations of
            even the most sophisticated library users. With it, your users can access everything your library has to
            offer from
            anywhere in the world, whether through an internal network, an Internet connection, or a wireless PDA.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://code.google.com/p/i-jetty
        </link>
        <image>ijetty_logo.png
        </image>
        <title>iJetty</title>
        <description>
            Jetty running on Android mobile device platform.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.ispaces.com/
        </link>
        <image>iSpaces.png
        </image>
        <title>iSpaces</title>
        <description>
            iSpaces is a virtual desktop where the state of your user interface is saved to the cloud meaning you can
            access
            your interface, as you left it, from any computer.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://jelastic.com/jetty-hosting
        </link>
        <image>jelastic.png
        </image>
        <title>Jelastic</title>
        <description>
            Jelastic is the next generation Java and PHP cloud hosting platform that can run and scale ANY Java or PHP
            application with no code changes required.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://j3unit.sourceforge.net
        </link>
        <image>j3unit.jpg
        </image>
        <title>J3Unit</title>
        <description>
            J3Unit is an object-oriented unit testing framework for JavaScript. J3Unit runs JavaScript tests directly in
            the web
            browser and can be automated using JUnit and Jetty. J3Unit builds on previous work by JSUnit and
            Script.aculo.us to
            provide a better way to automate JavaScript unit tests. Object-oriented JavaScript unit tests are written
            using the
            Script.aculo.us Test.Unit.Runner object, which is in turn built upon the prototype JavaScript library.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://jalbum.net
        </link>
        <image>jalbum.png
        </image>
        <title>JAlbum</title>
        <description>
            Drop folders containing image and movie files onto JAlbum. JAlbum will create thumbnails of your images and
            display
            them in index pages in HTML. You can also have JAlbum produce slide shows of your images for easy
            navigation. The
            apperance of the generated albums can be fully configured through the use of skins. The whole album is then
            uploaded
            to an FTP server by JAlbum or shared straight from your hard disk with JAlbum's integrated web server
            (Jetty).
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.jamonapi.com/
        </link>
        <image>jamon.jpg
        </image>
        <title>JAMon</title>
        <description>
            The Java Application Monitor (JAMon) is a free, simple, high performance, thread safe, Java API that allows
            developers to easily monitor production applications. JAMon was developed primarily for monitoring J2EE
            applications, however it can be used in any JDK environment. JAMon can be used in Servlets, JSP's, EJB's and
            Java
            Beans. JAMon is particularly useful in multithreaded software like a database engine.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://sourceforge.net/items/jboss
        </link>
        <image>jboss-logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>JBoss</title>
        <description>
            JBoss is an Open Source, standards-compliant, application server implemented in 100% Pure Java and
            distributed for
            free.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.ronri-kobo.com/English/JbyJ.html
        </link>
        <image>JbyJ1.gif
        </image>
        <title>JbyJ</title>
        <description>
            JbyJ is a plug-in that supplies 4D with following abilities: (1) JbyJ allows 4D to connect to other 4D in a
            network
            and call its item methods. (2) JbyJ allows Java programs (JSP, servlet, applet, application and so on) to
            connect
            to 4D in a network and call its item methods.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://jakarta.apache.org/commons/sandbox/jelly/
        </link>
        <image>jelly.gif
        </image>
        <title>Jelly</title>
        <description>
            <em>Jelly</em>
            is a tool for turning XML into executable code. So Jelly is a Java and XML based scripting and processing
            engine.&nbsp;
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.huihoo.org/jfox
        </link>
        <image>jfox.jpg
        </image>
        <title>JFox</title>
        <description>
            JFox is an Open Source, standards-compliant, J2EE based application server implemented in 100% Pure Java, It
            comes
            from China Enterprise Open Source Community. (www.huihoo.org)
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://eclipse.org/jgit/
        </link>
        <image>egit2.png
        </image>
        <title>JGit</title>
        <description>
            JGit is an EDL (new-style BSD) licensed, lightweight, pure Java library implementing the Git version control
            system.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://jimagedb.sourceforge.net/
        </link>
        <image>JImageDB50.png
        </image>
        <title>JImageDB</title>
        <description>
            JImageDB is a system of applications for creating, displaying, and maintaining a categorized,
            keyword-searchable
            database of images.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.atlassian.com/software/jira/docs/servers/jetty.jsp
        </link>
        <image>jira_splash.gif
        </image>
        <title>Atlassian - JIRA</title>
        <description>
            JIRA is a J2EE-based, issue tracking and item management application
            developed to make this process easier for your team.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.jmanage.org/
        </link>
        <image>jmanage.gif
        </image>
        <title>jManage</title>
        <description>
            jManage is an open source application management platform, which provides a centralized console for managing
            application clusters and distributed-application environments. jManage platform provides advanced features
            like
            Dashboards, Alerts, Graphs, Connectors, Security, SNMP support and more.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.objectweb.org/jonas/
        </link>
        <image>jonas.jpg
        </image>
        <title>JOnAS</title>
        <description>
            <strong>JOnAS</strong>
            is the Open Source implementation by
            <a href="https://www.objectweb.org/">ObjectWeb</a>
            of the J2EE
            <sup>TM</sup>
            <a href="https://java.sun.com/j2ee">specification</a>.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.jopera.org/
        </link>
        <image>jopera.jpg
        </image>
        <title>JOpera</title>
        <description>
            JOpera targets developers of Service-Oriented Business Applications and provides them with tools for rapid
            service
            composition. It includes a visual modeling environment, a light-weight execution engine, and also powerful
            debugging/refactoring tools which natively support the iterative nature of service composition.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://marsrover.nasa.gov/home/index.html
        </link>
        <image>mer.jpg
        </image>
        <title>JPL</title>
        <description>
            JPL uses Jetty for mission operations planning on a number of items, not the least of which is the Mars
            Rover
            programme.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.jpos.org
        </link>
        <image>jpos.jpg
        </image>
        <title>jPos</title>
        <description>
            jPOS is a Java[tm] platform based mission critical financial transaction library/framework that can be
            customized
            and extended in order to implement financial interchanges.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://jreceiver.sourceforge.net/index.html#acknowledgements
        </link>
        <image>jreceiver.gif
        </image>
        <title>JReceiver Audio Server</title>
        <description>
            JReceiver is a servlet-based audio server which features tightly integrated metadata indexing capabilities,
            browser-based management, an XML-RPC interface and support for network-based MP3 players like the Rio
            Receiver from
            Sonic Blue.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://jruby.codehaus.org/
        </link>
        <image>jruby.png
        </image>
        <title>JRuby</title>
        <description>
            JRuby Rails integration gives you a rake plugin which allows you to package your app as a webapp and try it
            out
            using Jetty.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://code.google.com/p/js-test-driver/</link>
        <title>JS Test Driver</title>
        <description>
            The goal of JsTestDriver is to build a JavaScript test runner which easily integrates with continuous builds
            systems
            and allows running tests on multiple browsers quickly to ease TDD style development.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.jtrac.info/
        </link>
        <image>jtrac.png
        </image>
        <title>JTrac</title>
        <description>
            JTrac is an open source and highly customizable issue-tracking web-application written in Java.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.jxta.org
        </link>
        <image>juxta.gif
        </image>
        <title>JXTA</title>
        <description>
            JXTA technology is a set of open protocols that allow any connected device on the network ranging from cell
            phones
            and wireless PDAs to PCs and servers to communicate and collaborate in a P2P manner.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.jzos.com
        </link>
        <image>jzos.gif
        </image>
        <title>JZOS</title>
        <description>
            The JZOS Java batch launcher and toolkit is a set of tools to simplify running Java on IBM mainframes under
            z/OS or
            OS/390.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://kettle.pentaho.org
        </link>
        <image>logo_kettle_lrg.png
        </image>
        <title>Kettle</title>
        <description>
            Kettle is a powerful tool designed to bridge the gap between business and ICT, turning your company's data
            into
            increased profits.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://kowari.sourceforge.net/
        </link>
        <image>kowari.gif
        </image>
        <title>kowari</title>
        <description>
            The Kowari Metastore(TM) is an Open Source, massively scalable, transaction-safe, purpose-built database for
            the
            storage and retrieval of metadata.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://kuali.org/rice/overview
        </link>
        <image>kuali-rice.png
        </image>
        <title>Kuali Rice</title>
        <description>
            The Kuali Rice software provides an enterprise class middleware suite of integrated products that allows for
            applications to be built in an agile fashion. This enables developers to react to end-user business
            requirements in
            an efficient and productive manner, so that they can produce high quality business applications.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.lawson.com/
        </link>
        <image>lawson.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Lawson Enterprise Search</title>
        <description>
            Lawson Enterprise Search is a comprehensive enterprise search and retrieval (ESR) platform that has the
            capability
            to search both structured and unstructured data across Lawson applications, including the S3 enterprise
            system
            Lawson Business Intelligence, as well as locally stored end-user data.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.liferay.com/
        </link>
        <image>liferay-logo.png
        </image>
        <title>Liferay Portal</title>
        <description>
            Liferay is the world's leading open source portal platform. Now in its sixth year of development, Liferay
            Portal is
            JSR-168 compliant and runs on almost any major application server, database, and operating system, rendering
            over
            700 deployment combinations. With over 50 portlets prebundled and more than 20 community-contributed themes
            available, Liferay Portal is unsurpassed in out-of-the-box functionality, bringing immediate usability and
            accelerated development potential to a broad swath of portal-based internet application scenarios.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://liftweb.net/
        </link>
        <image>lift.png
        </image>
        <title>lift Web Framework</title>
        <description>
            lift is yet another web development framework. lift runs inside a Java web container and uses the Scala
            programming
            language for coding. lift stresses security, developer productivity, ease of deployment, ease of
            maintainability,
            performance, and compatibility with existing systems. lift borrows from the best of existing frameworks
            including
            Seaside's highly granular sessions and security, Rails fast flash-to-bang, Django's "more than just CRUD is
            included", and Erlyweb's scalability for Comet-style applications.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://langagelinotte.free.fr/
        </link>
        <image>linotte_pixel.png
        </image>
        <title>Linotte</title>
        <description>
            Linotte is a very simple programming language which is inspired by French syntax. Linotte help beginner in
            computer
            science to discover imperative programming and functional programming. The vocabulary used is very simple
            and easy
            to learn, it makes this language accessible for children (a program is a book, display is a paint ...). You
            can
            create website with integrated server Jetty.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.lockss.org/
        </link>
        <image>lockss.gif
        </image>
        <title>LOCKSS</title>
        <description>
            The LOCKSS Program is an inexpensive, practical solution to digital preservation and access. The foundation
            of a
            library is its collections. If libraries fail to build digital collections they will cease to be libraries.
            Without
            libraries society loses one of its two memory organizations (the other being museums). If libraries don't
            step up to
            this responsibility they will, in effect, be creating a digital dark age for future generations. With a
            publisher's
            permission, the LOCKSS Program allows libraries to fulfill this societal obligation, easily and affordably
            building
            digital collections.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.logperspective.com
        </link>
        <image>logperspective.jpg
        </image>
        <title>LogPerspective</title>
        <description>
            LogPerspective simplifies analysis and problem tracking in modern applications by
            providing consolidated view on log files. LogPerspective is completely independent from
            log-producers. It studies log output generated by existing applications or scripts eliminating the
            need for integration development.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://cwiki.apache.org/labs/magma.html
        </link>
        <image>magma.png
        </image>
        <title>Magma</title>
        <description>
            Magma provides an innovative, effective framework for delivering enterprise level Java web applications,
            coding
            faster and easier than before, while maximizing code reuse and integration possibilities.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://maven.apache.org
        </link>
        <image>maven.png
        </image>
        <title>Maven</title>
        <description>
            Maven is a software item management and comprehension tool. Based on the concept of a item object
            model (POM),
            Maven can manage a item's build, reporting and documentation from a central piece of information.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.mec-as2.org/products_mec_as2.php
        </link>
        <image>mecas2.gif
        </image>
        <title>m-e-c as2</title>
        <description>
            m-e-c as2 is a EDIINT AS2 implementation. It contains a comfortable logging- and configuration GUI that
            helps you
            managing your transactions. It supports asynchronous and synchronous MDN, digital signatures, encryption,
            SSL.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.melati.org/index.html
        </link>
        <image>melati.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Melati</title>
        <description>
            Melati is a tool for building Java-programmed websites backed by a database or accessing a database over
            HTTP.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://opensource.mendelson-e-c.com/
        </link>
        <image>mecas2.gif
        </image>
        <title>Mendelson OpenSource AS2</title>
        <description>
            Mendelson OpenSource AS2 is a EDIINT AS2 implementation. It contains a comfortable logging- and
            configuration GUI
            that helps you managing your transactions. It supports asynchronous and synchronous MDN, digital signatures,
            encryption, SSL.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://studios.thoughtworks.com/mingle-item-intelligence
        </link>
        <image>mingle_header.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Mingle</title>
        <description>
            Mingle is a software application that helps you and your team manage Agile IT items. It supports software
            delivery by providing the whole team with a single place to share all item output using a framework based
            on over
            7 years of ThoughtWorks' Agile experience. Mingle provides item intelligence for teams that need to make
            real-time decisions based on Agile metrics collected from everyday activities.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.mirthcorp.com/
        </link>
        <image>mirthcorplogo.png
        </image>
        <title>Mirth</title>
        <description>
            The Mirth item – founded, incubated and supported commercially by the company – aims to transform health
            information technology by making high-value information technology solutions available to the healthcare
            community
            on an open source basis. Our professional grade, service-backed open source offerings break through the cost
            barriers to achieving more rapid health information technology dissemination, and enable our customers and
            users to
            create a safer and more effective healthcare delivery system.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://mms.10gen.com/
        </link>
        <image>mongo-10gen.png
        </image>
        <title>MongoDB Management Service (MMS)</title>
        <description>
            MongoDB Management Service (MMS) is a cloud-based suite of services for managing MongoDB deployments. MMS
            provides
            monitoring and backup capabilities, helping users optimize clusters, automate tasks and mitigate operational
            risk.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://mop.fusesource.org/
        </link>
        <image>mop-logo.png
        </image>
        <title>Mop</title>
        <description>
            MOP is a small utility for executing Java programs which are stored as artifacts like jars or bundles in a
            Maven
            repository. MOP automatically deals with the following for you: transitive dependencies; downloading
            artifacts from
            remote repositories and caching them locally; setting up your classpath.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.mx4j.org
        </link>
        <image>mx4j.gif
        </image>
        <title>MX4J</title>
        <description>
            MX4J is a item to build an Open Source implementation of the Java(TM) Management Extensions (JMX) and of
            the JMX
            Remote API (JSR 160) specifications, and to build tools relating
            to JMX
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.nabble.com
        </link>
        <image>nabble.gif
        </image>
        <title>Nabble</title>
        <description>
            Free Hosted Public Forums. Our forums are truly public, democratic and absolutely free. Nabble's advanced
            community
            filtering gives you only the best content without the need for moderation. Find forums that interest you or
            easily
            start your own in minutes.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.nakedobjects.org/
        </link>
        <image>nakedObjects.png
        </image>
        <title>Naked Objects</title>
        <description>
            Naked Objects for Java is a full-stack open source application development framework, designed to let you
            rapidly
            develop domain-driven business applications.The framework is called Naked Objects because all you need to
            develop
            are your pojo domain objects - the Naked Objects framework auto-creates an object-oriented user interface
            (OOUI),
            either as a desktop app or as a webapp. You can also choose where and how to persist your domain objects.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.nds.com
        </link>
        <image>nds.gif
        </image>
        <title>NDS</title>
        <description>
            NDS, a majority owned subsidiary of News Corporation, supplies open end-to-end digital technology and
            services to
            digital pay-television platform operators and content providers.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://nexus.sonatype.org/
        </link>
        <image>nexus.png
        </image>
        <title>Nexus</title>
        <description>
            Nexus is a powerful and robust Maven repository manager, created to provide reliable access to artifacts
            required
            for development and provisioning. Maven's central repository has always served as a great convenience for
            users of
            Maven, but it has always been recommended to maintain your own repositories to ensure stability within your
            organization. Nexus greatly simplifies the maintenance of your own internal repositories and access to
            external
            repositories. With Nexus you can completely control access to, and deployment of, every artifact in your
            organization from a single location.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.ngasi.com/
        </link>
        <image>ngasi.png
        </image>
        <title>NGASI</title>
        <description>
            NGASI AppServer Manager was designed with hosted environments in mind.NGASI AppServer Manager enables
            Private JVM
            JAVA Hosting on a shared server for multiple accounts.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.queuing.com/methodize.org/nntprss/
        </link>
        <image>nntprss.gif
        </image>
        <title>nntp//rss</title>
        <description>
            Bridging the worlds of NNTP clients and RSS feeds, nntp//rss is an application that will enable you to use
            your
            existing favorite NNTP newsreader to read your information channels.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.nuxeo.org/
        </link>
        <image>nuxeo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Nuxeo</title>
        <description>
            Nuxeo delivers an open source document management application built with a complete, modular and extensible
            open
            source software platform for enterprise content management. Other packaged applications built with the
            platform
            provide solutions for digital asset management and case management.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://openadaptor3.openadaptor.org/
        </link>
        <image>openadaptor_logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>Openadaptor</title>
        <description>
            Openadaptor is an Open Source toolkit for Enterprise Application Integration. It provides software
            components for
            connecting to a variety of transports (e.g. JMS, RDBMS, SOAP, HTTP, Files) and components for working with
            different
            data representations (e.g. XML, JDBC result sets, fixed width and delimited string records). Its design lays
            emphasis on ease-of-use, flexibility and minimal time required for assembling production quality adaptors.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.igniterealtime.org
        </link>
        <image>openfire_logo_wide.png
        </image>
        <title>Openfire</title>
        <description>
            Openfire, formerly called Wildfire, is a real time collaboration (RTC) server dual-licensed under the Open
            Source
            GPL and commercially. It uses the only widely adopted open protocol for instant messaging, XMPP (also called
            Jabber). Openfire is incredibly easy to setup and administer, but offers rock-solid security and
            performance.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.opennms.org/
        </link>
        <image>opennms.png
        </image>
        <title>OpenNMS</title>
        <description>
            OpenNMS is the world's first enterprise grade network management platform developed under the open source
            model. It
            consists of a community supported open-source item as well as a commercial services, training, and
            support
            organization.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.ofbiz.org
        </link>
        <image>ofbiz.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Open For Business</title>
        <description>
            An open source enterprise automation software item. The goal of the item is to create an open source
            application framework, application components, and suite of enterprise applications.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://oreports.sourceforge.net/</link>
        <title>OpenReports</title>
        <description>
            OpenReports is a complete reporting solution that provides the ability for users to view dynamically created
            PDF
            reports in a browser.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://openshift.redhat.com/
        </link>
        <image>openshift-logo-medium.png
        </image>
        <title>OpenShift</title>
        <description>
            OpenShift is Red Hat's free, auto-scaling Platform as a Service (PaaS) for applications. As an application
            platform
            in the cloud, OpenShift manages the stack so you can focus on your code.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.lilacsoftware.com/orcahome.html
        </link>
        <image>orcass1.gif
        </image>
        <title>Orca</title>
        <description>
            Orca is a high performance client/server application for organizing and playing audio files (initially MP3
            and Ogg
            Vorbis).
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://oscar-osgi.sourceforge.net/
        </link>
        <image>oscar.gif
        </image>
        <title>Oscar</title>
        <description>
            This bundle is an implementation of the OSGi HTTP Service, Version 1.1. It is built on top of a
            slightly modified version of Jetty
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://github.com/RootServices/otter</link>
        <title>Otter</title>
        <description>
            Otter is a stateless micro web framework powered by Jetty. It uses async I/O, prefers to run in an embedded
            servlet
            container, has regex routing, includes built-in RESTful support, and has CSRF protection.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.ozibug.com
        </link>
        <image>ozibug.gif
        </image>
        <title>Ozibug</title>
        <description>
            Ozibug is a platform-independent, web-based bug tracking system which can be installed and run straight out
            of the
            box on any Java servlet capable platform.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.opnet.com/solutions/application_performance/panorama.html
        </link>
        <image>panorama.gif
        </image>
        <title>Panorama</title>
        <description>
            OPNET Panorama(TM) delivers comprehensive performance management for critical Java and .NET applications
            throughout
            the application lifecycle, beginning with development and QA, and continuing through deployment and
            operations.
            Panorama continuously monitors thousands of system and application metrics within each server, across all
            tiers, and
            automatically spots performance anomalies with advanced deviation tracking. Panorama's unique correlation
            technology
            automatically detects patterns in metrics and events, identifying cause-and-effect relationships and
            pinpointing
            symptoms that might otherwise go undetected. With deep transaction tracing from within the Java Virtual
            Machine
            (JVM) and the .NET Common Language Runtime (CLR) virtual machine, Panorama provides method-level visibility
            into
            application code, enabling root-cause analysis and rapid problem remediation.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://forge.novell.com/modules/xfmod/item/?panther
        </link>
        <image>panther.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Panther</title>
        <description>
            Panther is a lightweight, modular Java application server, suitable for embedding in a web server. The
            intention of
            the item is not to duplicate all the functionality found in a J2EE app server, rather just some of the
            most
            commonly used features.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://wiki.ops4j.org/confluence/display/ops4j/Pax+Web
        </link>
        <image>paxweb-logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>Pax Web</title>
        <description>
            Pax Web is an implementation of OSGi R4 Http Service using Jetty 6.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.verit.de/products/index.html
        </link>
        <image>petalogo.gif
        </image>
        <title>PETA</title>
        <description>
            PETA is a platform for automated testing of software systems. These include service oriented architectures
            (SOA),
            n-tier/multi-tier architectures (J2EE, .NET), webservices, client/server applications and browser based web
            applications. PETA can both be employed for functional testing purposes like regression-, integration- or
            system
            tests as well as non-functional load or stress tests.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.pixory.org
        </link>
        <image>pixory.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Pixory Personal Image Server</title>
        <description>
            Pixory allows you to store your photos on your own pc but to access, compose into albums, and share them
            anywhere on
            the internet.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.polarrose.com
        </link>
        <image>polarrose_logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>Polar Rose</title>
        <description>
            The web is increasingly becoming visually oriented, progressing from text to photos and other rich media.
            Close to
            10 million new photos are uploaded on a daily basis, a number which is doubling every eight to ten months.
            Photos
            tell many stories, but unlike text, the context of a photo is hard to search for unless explicitly
            "translated" by a
            human being. The photo web of today is like the text web before Altavista, Inktomi, and Google. Polar Rose
            makes
            photos searchable by analyzing their content and recognizing the people in them.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.item-drive.net/
        </link>
        <image>itemDriveLogo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>item Drive</title>
        <description>
            item Management Software - item Drive. Online, secure and fully customizable. It offers Gantt charts
            calendaring and collaboration. Everything to drive your items to success!
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.protekt.com/index.html
        </link>
        <image>protekt.png
        </image>
        <title>Protekt</title>
        <description>
            Protekt Encryption is an all Java
            implementation of TLS version 1 (including backwards
            compatibility with Netscape's SSL protocol version 3).
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://jakarta.apache.org/avalon/phoenix/index.html
        </link>
        <image>phoenix.gif
        </image>
        <title>Phoenix</title>
        <description>
            Phoenix is a micro-kernel designed and implemented on top of the Avalon framework. It is both an API to
            program to
            and a reference implementation. The reference implementation provides a number of facilities to manage the
            environment of Server Applications.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.primrose.org.uk
        </link>
        <image>primrose_logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Primrose</title>
        <description>
            Primrose is an open-source java database connection pool that is packed with features for developers and
            sys-admins
            that want exceptional control over how their applications interact with their database. A mature product,
            Primrose
            provides excellent configuration of pools, email-based notification of 'crisis pool events' as well as
            dynamic
            administration and monitoring of database interaction and SQL transactions via a JMX driven web-page.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.pulptunes.com/
        </link>
        <image>pulptunes.png
        </image>
        <title>PulpTunes</title>
        <description>
            PulpTunes is a web server (powered by Jetty) for the iTunes desktop app, letting you access your music
            through the
            Web. It runs on Windows, Mac, and any other platform like Linux, provided you have an iTunes-like XML
            library
            declaring the path of the music files.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.dse.se
        </link>
        <image>dse_pulsar.gif
        </image>
        <title>Pulsar</title>
        <description>
            Pulsar is a modularized web architecture, providing a complete framework and a rich toolbox for web
            applications,
            covering the phases of development, deployment and maintenance. Furthermore Pulsar provides a structure for
            partitioning applications into the layers of business logic, user interface logic and user interface layout.
            Pulsar
            is in itself also a server/container in which the applications can execute. As a server Pulsar provides
            commonly
            needed functionality for Web Applications such as user management, permission management and application
            monitoring.
            Since version 1.8 Pulsar embeds Jetty as the preferred HTTP transport engine.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.riadiffusion.com/
        </link>
        <image>Push-logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Push Technology</title>
        <description>
            Diffusion is a bi-directional push engine developed by Push Technology to allow customers to stream highly
            volatile
            data to a web browser without the need to install any software on the end-users PC. Diffusion looked to
            Jetty for
            its XmlHttpRequest engine as well as its Web Server. As Diffusion offers a massively saleable Push
            Technology for
            web browsers, Jetty with it Continuations was chosen as a proven method.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.quantmethods.com/
        </link>
        <image>QMS.gif
        </image>
        <title>QuantMethods QMS</title>
        <description>
            QuantMethods QMS application contains modules for the most frequently taught mathematical models used in
            quantitative decision making at an
            introductory level including, but not limited to, linear programming, network, forecasting, inventory and
            production, and dynamic programming models. The application is offered over the web on a subscription basis
            and as a
            standalone application that can be installed on Windows, Mac OS X, Linux, or other Unix based systems.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.ifountain.com/rapidinsight
        </link>
        <image>rapidinsight_banner.png
        </image>
        <title>Rapid Insight</title>
        <description>
            RapidInsight is a flexible solution to rapidly implement active dashboards that present relevant information
            from
            disparate systems to users in near real-time. RapidInsight dashboards can be implemented in a fraction of
            the time
            and effort typically required to implement traditional solutions. RapidInsight is the perfect solution to
            implement
            interactive dashboards that are tailored to the needs of each user, providing a unified, consistent
            interface to the
            relevant information, collected from variety of disparate data sources rapidly.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.reddogsoftware.com/?p=Products
        </link>
        <image>reddog202.jpg
        </image>
        <title>ReadyPortal</title>
        <description>
            ReadyPortal is a comprehensive, turn-key Web presence solution that allows you to create a Web site at a
            fraction of
            the cost and effort required by traditional Web development. Available in both hosted and software packages,
            ReadyPortal can fit easily into organizations of any size. Its user-friendly interface and template-based
            publishing
            system make your ReadyPortal site easy to maintain and evolve. Non-technical users as well as IT
            professionals can
            modify and update content, features and functionality any time, from anywhere Internet access is available.
            This
            enables you to keep your site fresh more easily than custom Web development, which requires more intimate
            technical
            expertise and often results in stagnant content.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.osflash.org/red5
        </link>
        <image>red5.gif
        </image>
        <title>Red5</title>
        <description>
            Red5 is a server that not only streams content to the Flash plugin, but it can push calls and information to
            the
            Flash client! It can also receive video/audio/data from a flash client and either save or rebroadcast that
            content.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://redline.st/
        </link>
        <image>redline.png
        </image>
        <title>RedlineSmalltalk</title>
        <description>
            Redline is a thoroughly modern version of Smalltalk that runs on the Java Virtual Machine.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://restlet.org
        </link>
        <image>restlet.gif
        </image>
        <title>Restlet Framework</title>
        <description>
            Brings the simplicity and efficiency of the REST architectural style to Java developers. Includes a
            connector
            powered by Jetty. Provided by Noelios Consulting (<a href="https://noelios.com">noelios.com</a>).
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.rewoo.de/produkt.html
        </link>
        <image>rewoo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>REWOO Technologies</title>
        <description>
            REWOO Scope is a modern and easy to use web-based enterprise content management system. It supports
            knowledge
            workers and managers in making the right decisions based upon all relevant information. Some of its key
            features are
            excel-like built-in formulas, automatic management of user rights and the possibility to create simple
            applications
            on top of REWOO Scope without any programming skills.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://rife.dev.java.net/
        </link>
        <image>rife-logo.png
        </image>
        <title>RIFE</title>
        <description>
            RIFE offers an alternative approach to web application development and design. It builds upon the Java
            platform, but
            offers all required tools and APIs to implement and perform all common website related tasks in a fast,
            intuitive,
            consistent and innovative manner.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://rubygems.org/gems/rjack-jetty
        </link>
        <image>rjackjetty.png
        </image>
        <title>rjack-jetty</title>
        <description>
            A gem packaging of the Jetty Web Server for JRuby: Provides jetty, jetty-util, servlet-api, and
            jetty-rewrite-handler
            jars. A Jetty::ServerFactory for simple programmatic server setup in ruby. A set of Jetty::TestServlets
            containing a
            SnoopServlet and PerfTestServlet (implemented in Java). A jetty-service bin script for easy testing from the
            command
            line. Note that JSP support is provided separately in the companion
            jetty-jsphttps://rjack.rubyforge.org/jetty-jsp/ gem.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.romaframework.org/
        </link>
        <image>roma.gif
        </image>
        <title>Roma Framework</title>
        <description>
            Roma is an Open Source initiative to make Java application development easy. The approach is totally DDD:
            let's
            think to the domain of your application and Roma will make the rest: persistence (database), presentation
            (HTML +
            Ajax), logging, reporting, user management, sessions, workflow, scheduler, etc. Roma is a Meta Framework
            titlely a
            tool that aims to remove dependencies between your application code and frameworks and tools you use. This
            allows
            you to change the technology at zero cost without any changes to your application code. Roma is also a MDA
            implementation since takes its concepts and philosophy but it's totally based on POJOs with no need to learn
            other
            micro languages and complex standards.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.rostrvm.com/?jetty
        </link>
        <image>rostrvmweblogo.gif
        </image>
        <title>rostrvm</title>
        <description>
            Rostrvm Solutions Limited is a software company. We design, develop and support the rostrvm suite of
            applications
            that make call centre technologies and contact management processes work efficiently and effectively. Jetty
            is
            embedded in the rostrvm product and provides access to web based real-time management information reports.
            It is
            also used to drive call centre agent wallboards that provide high impact operational data.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www-uk.hpl.hp.com/people/afs/Joseki/doc/JosekiSever.html</link>
        <title>RDF Server</title>
        <description>
            The Joseki server provides a way of publishes RDF data and providing access via RDQL.&nbsp;
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.dracoware.com/rsp.php
        </link>
        <image>rsp.gif
        </image>
        <title>RSP Network Monitor</title>
        <description>
            RSP is a network monitoring solution which allows IT teams to collaboratively solve problems. RSP does this
            by
            utilizing an incident-tracking interface, allowing team members to better coordinate their efforts at
            solving
            problems, and to record their solutions. RSP also contains a number of other useful features such as remote
            configuration through the web interface, security with SSL, and builtin analysis and graphing tools.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.blazeworks.biz
        </link>
        <image>LogoSabercat.gif
        </image>
        <title>Sabercat</title>
        <description>
            A UDDI web services registry for private environments.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.sagetv.com/
        </link>
        <image>sagetv.jpg
        </image>
        <title>SageTV</title>
        <description>
            SageTV is an industry-leading software technology that allows users to create and operate complete media
            centers
            from an existing PC.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.seatrafcell.com/
        </link>
        <image>seatrafcell.jpg
        </image>
        <title>SeaTrafCell</title>
        <description>
            SeaTrafCell displays traffic information from the puget sound area (Seattle) on Java (J2ME) enabled
            cellphones.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.openqa.org/selenium-rc/</link>
        <image>
        </image>
        <title>Selenium-RC</title>
        <description>
            Selenium Remote Control is a test tool that allows you to write automated web application UI tests in any
            programming language against any HTTP website using any mainstream JavaScript-enabled browser.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://servicemix.apache.org/home.html
        </link>
        <image>servicemix.png
        </image>
        <title>ServiceMix</title>
        <description>
            Apache ServiceMix is an open source ESB (Enterprise Service Bus) that combines the functionality of a
            Service
            Oriented Architecture (SOA) and an Event Driven Architecture (EDA) to create an agile, enterprise ESB.
            Apache
            ServiceMix is an open source distributed ESB built from the ground up on the Java Business Integration (JBI)
            specification JSR 208 and released under the Apache license. The goal of JBI is to allow components and
            services to
            be integrated in a vendor independent way, allowing users and vendors to plug and play. Apache ServiceMix
            uses Jetty
            in servicemix-http component (client and server).
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.servlets.com
        </link>
        <image>servlets.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Servlets.com</title>
        <description>
            Popular portal site for all things servlet programming related.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.source-code.biz/ServletViewer/</link>
        <image>
        </image>
        <title>Servlet Viewer</title>
        <description>
            ServletViewer is a Java program that can load a Java servlet and display its output. It uses an embedded
            HTTP server
            (Jetty) and an embedded web browser (SWT Browser widget). ServletViewer can be used to run a Java servlet
            web
            application as a stand-alone program on the local computer.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://incubator.apache.org/shindig/
        </link>
        <image>shindig.png
        </image>
        <title>Shindig</title>
        <description>
            Shindig is an OpenSocial container and helps you to start hosting OpenSocial apps quickly by providing the
            code to
            render gadgets, proxy requests, and handle REST and RPC requests. Shindig's goal is to allow new sites to
            start
            hosting social apps in under an hour's worth of work.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.simplecenter.org/
        </link>
        <image>simple_center.jpg
        </image>
        <title>SimpleCenter</title>
        <description>
            SimpleCenter is the future of digital media management ... an opensource alternative for acquiring,
            organizing,
            experiencing, distributing and sharing your music, photos, movies, podcasts and more.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.datarepresentations.com/products/enterprise/standard/index.jsp
        </link>
        <image>enterpriseLiteLogo.gif
        </image>
        <title>Simplicity Enterprise</title>
        <description>
            Simplicity Enterprise rapid application development tool allows you to aggregate data from many sources in
            an
            intuitive graphical interface, and transform that very same data into robust web applications in minutes.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.smartbase.sk/
        </link>
        <image>smartbase_logo.png
        </image>
        <title>SmartBase</title>
        <description>
            SmartBase is a knowledge base servant archiving, sorting and searching knowledge. The system allows
            searching
            content of PDF, DOC, XLS, PPT and many others of file types. A demo application is available at
            https://demo.smartbase.sk.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.smartfoxserver.com/
        </link>
        <image>smartfox.png
        </image>
        <title>SmartFoxServer</title>
        <description>
            SmartFoxServer is a comprehensive and powerful platform for rapidly developing multiuser applications and
            games with
            Macromedia Flash MX, MX 2004, 8, Flex 2 and Flash CS3. It was developed with simplicity in mind, allowing
            developers
            to quickly create any type of multiplayer interactions, from basic chat applications to the most complex
            real-time
            games. SmartFoxServer comes with a rich set of features, one of the best sets of documentations with many
            source
            examples, powerful administration tools and an active online support forum.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://snipsnap.org
        </link>
        <image>snipsnap-logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>SnipSnap</title>
        <description>
            SnipSnap is a free and easy to install Weblog and Wiki Software written in Java.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.softwaredemo.com/
        </link>
        <image>softwaredemo.png
        </image>
        <title>SoftwareDEMO</title>
        <description>
            SoftwareDEMO is a cloud platform that enables desktop based software to be provided as a cloud service. It
            does not
            only include hosting and runtime environment but also user management and billing for software vendors.
            SoftwareDEMO
            uses Jetty as an embedded servlet container for its connector application SWD Agent.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.sonicsoftware.com/
        </link>
        <image>sonic_logo_popup1.gif
        </image>
        <title>Sonic MQ</title>
        <description>
            SonicMQ&#174; is the industry's most reliable message server, delivering unsurpassed scalability, extensive
            connectivity, and comprehensive security for business-critical communication across the extended enterprise.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.spiderline.com/
        </link>
        <image>spiderline.gif
        </image>
        <title>Spiderline</title>
        <description>
            Spiderline(TM) is a fully customizable hosted search engine service offering lightning fast searches of
            intranet or
            individual/business websites. Spiderline has been providing services to individuals, small businesses and
            governmental agencies since 1999.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://spindle.sourceforge.net/
        </link>
        <image>spindle.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Spindle</title>
        <description>
            Eclipse plugins for running Tapestry and Jetty.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.springframework.org/
        </link>
        <image>springframework.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Spring Framework</title>
        <description>
            The spring framework is an application framework supporting JEE(tm) style applications. Spring supports
            Jetty as a
            HTTP service in their Spring Dynamic Modules for OSGi(tm) Service Platforms, or jetty can be simply embedded
            in the
            spring framework directly or as an xbean.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.stratiforms.com/index.html
        </link>
        <image>stratlogoCap.gif
        </image>
        <title>StratiForms</title>
        <description>
            StratiForms allows you to create an eForms solution for your business. Itis a Java Servlet container web
            application
            using Java Server Pages (jsp), Java Servlets, and complex Java Objects.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.structuredsoft.com
        </link>
        <image>structuredj.jpg
        </image>
        <title>StructuredJ</title>
        <description>
            StructuredJ&#174; is the industry's most powerful 'procedural' Java-based Web application scripting system,
            delivering unsurpassed productivity and simplicity to J2EE development for developers making the move to
            Java.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://subsonic.sourceforge.net/
        </link>
        <image>subsonic.png
        </image>
        <title>Subsonic</title>
        <description>
            Subsonic is a free, web-based media streamer, providing ubiquitous access to your music. Use it to share
            your music
            with friends, or to listen to your own music while at work. You can stream to multiple players
            simultaneously, for
            instance to one player in your kitchen and another in your living room.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.sunnyvale.it/
        </link>
        <image>sunnyvale.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Sunnyvale ALA</title>
        <description>
            Sunnyvale releases A.L.A., the Adapter-Logic Application that aims to be the smallest, fast, scalable and
            cheap
            integration framework acting as glue in an heterogeneous application environment and allowing different
            platform to
            talk together. Built by pluggable front-end/back-end components and based only on open standards, Sunnyvale
            A.L.A.
            is Java powered and benefits from Jetty in its SOAP Controller servlet. "Jetty gives A.L.A. the possibility
            to
            expose an HTTP/SOAP interface to the external world without the constraint of an heavy and expensive
            Application
            Server behind" says Denis Maggiorotto, the A.L.A. designer and Sunnyvale C.E.O. "Jetty is embeddable, fast
            and
            consumes scarce computational resources; thanks to it A.L.A. is taking the place of many other application
            adapters."
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.systinet.com/products/overview
        </link>
        <image>systinet.gif
        </image>
        <title>Systinet WASP</title>
        <description>
            Systinet's products enable, publish, discover, govern and manage SOA business services, and make it easy to
            build
            secure and reliable Web services with Java and C++ applications.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.tangosol.com/
        </link>
        <image>tangosol-flat-inline.gif
        </image>
        <title>Tangosol Coherence</title>
        <description>
            Tangosol Coherence&#8482; enables clustered in-memory object sharing, caching and management among multiple
            instances of Java applications with unparalleled scalable performance, availability, and reliability.
            Tangosol
            Coherence*Web&#8482; brings the benefits of Coherence to HTTP Session management in applications deployed on
            Jetty
            without requiring any code changes. Installed on a deployable Jetty application, Coherence*Web assures the
            highest
            HTTP Session reliability and availability by removing all single points of failure, provides linear
            scalability up
            to hundreds of servers, and delivers extreme performance, even with huge HTTP Sessions.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://jakarta.apache.org/tapestry
        </link>
        <image>tapestry.png
        </image>
        <title>Tapestry</title>
        <description>
            Tapestry is a powerful, open-source, all-Java framework for creating leading edge web applications in Java.
            Tapestry
            is an alternative to scripting environments such as JavaServer Pages or Velocity. Tapestry goes far further,
            providing a complete framework for creating extremely dynamic applications with minimal amounts of coding.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.tipp24.de
        </link>
        <image>tipp24_logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Tipp24</title>
        <description>
            About Tipp24 AG: Tipp24 was established in 1999 and is now the market leader for lottery products in the
            Internet on
            the basis of billings. The company has succeeded in achieving impressive growth rates right from the start.
            Almost
            all state lottery products are supplied. It only takes a few mouse clicks to buy a lottery ticket - round
            the clock,
            quickly and anonymously. The ticket receipt is kept safely, winners are notified about their prizes
            automatically by
            text message and e-mail and prizes are credited automatically. No extra charge is made for this service.
            Subsidiaries of Tipp24 (<a href="https://www.tipp24.de">https://www.tipp24.de</a>) are Ventura24 in Spain
            (<a
                href="https://www.ventura24.es">https://www.ventura24.es</a>) and Puntogioco24 (<a
                href="https://www.puntogioco24.it">https://www.puntogioco24.it</a>) in Italy.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.tivoli.com/
        </link>
        <image>netview.gif
        </image>
        <title>IBM Tivoli NetView</title>
        <description>
            IBM Tivoli NetView discovers TCP/IP networks, displays network topologies, correlates and manages events and
            SNMP
            traps, monitors network health, and gathers performance data.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://topfox.co.uk/
        </link>
        <image>TopFox.gif
        </image>
        <title>Top Fox Competitions</title>
        <description>
            TopFox is a white-label competition network and co-registration technology, powering over 30 top UK web
            properties
            competition areas and has a million+ active members.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.trackstudio.com/
        </link>
        <image>trackstudio.gif
        </image>
        <title>Track Studio</title>
        <description>
            TrackStudio is one of the most powerful issue tracking systems based on Java. The high performance rates and
            scalability, support of nearly all servlet containers and DBMSs as well as the affordable price make this
            system a
            perfect choice for many companies.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.ws02.com
        </link>
        <image>tungsten_logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>Tungsten</title>
        <description>
            WSO2 Tungsten is an application server for Web services, fully open source and licensed under the Apache
            Software
            License. With its built in high-performance Web server, full support for XML, SOAP, WSDL, and support for
            reliable,
            secure communications, Tungsten makes it simple and effective to create, consume and manage Web services.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.vmware.com/
        </link>
        <image>vmware.png
        </image>
        <title>vmware</title>
        <description>
            Simplify management of VMware vSphere by automating patches and updates. VMware vCenter Update Manager makes
            it easy
            to manage tracking and patching of VMware vSphere hosts, as well as select Windows virtual machines.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.vodafone360.com/en/web/home/index
        </link>
        <image>Vodafone.png
        </image>
        <title>Vodafone</title>
        <description>
            360 is a new internet service for your mobile, PC and Mac. It brings your phone, email, chat and social
            network
            contacts together in one place. Communicate with your friends, see their status updates, share your photos
            and
            favourite places – from your phone, PC or Mac.
            Jetty is a critical part of the Vodafone 360 infrastructure. Jetty Continuations give us an edge in
            performance for
            COMET and long-polling applications with thousands of concurrently connected users. Jetty's simplicity and
            reliability has been a productivity gain throughout the item - Phil Jeffrey Principle Development
            Manager,
            Vodafone 360
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://wadi.codehaus.org/
        </link>
        <image>wadi.gif
        </image>
        <title>WADI</title>
        <description>
            WADI is an acronym of 'Web Application Distribution Infrastructure'. WADI's aim is to resolve many of the
            problems
            of dealing with state in the clustered J2EE Web Tier. This involves HttpSession replication, migration and
            relocation.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.themidnightcoders.com/weborb
        </link>
        <image>mc-logo.gif
        </image>
        <title>WebORB</title>
        <description>
            WebORB is a development platform and a runtime environment for Rich Internet Applications. Supported types
            of rich
            clients include AJAX and Flash Remoting. WebORB provides a connectivity framework between client
            applications and a
            variety of server-side components including POJOs, EJB, XML web services and ColdFusion. Product features
            include
            zero-configuration deployment, code-access security, object activation, dynamic type adaptation and many
            more. Live
            examples are available at: https://www.themidnightcoders.com/examples
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://words.jspell.com/
        </link>
        <image>wordexplorer_logo.png
        </image>
        <title>Word Explorer</title>
        <description>
            Word Explorer is a word game word finder, anagram solver and visual dictionary. Use Word Explorer to lookup
            words in
            English, find scrabble words, search for suffixes, prefixes and more. Word Explorer uses a responsive design
            and is
            compatible with desktop and mobile devices.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.wikileaksforum.net/topic/super-easy-wikileaks-mirror-server
        </link>
        <image>wikileaks.png
        </image>
        <title>WikiLeaks</title>
        <description>
            This is a java executable that contains both the WL website and a webserver in less than 30Mbytes.On any
            computer it
            will start a WIKILEAKS website and will serve HTTP and HTTPS protocols.This should make it easier for
            anybody to
            have its own mirror. Users can redirect the ports to give access from the internet or simply browse it in
            their own
            computers.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://wings.mercatis.de/
        </link>
        <image>wings.gif
        </image>
        <title>wingS</title>
        <description>
            In a nutshell, wingS is a web application framework based on Java Servlets, resembling the Swing API with
            its MVC
            paradigm and providing a versatile template mechanism enabling you to separate logic and design
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://xgql.sourceforge.net/
        </link>
        <image>Xgql_logo.jpg
        </image>
        <title>XGQL</title>
        <description>
            XGQL is a middleware allowing to access and format data from heterogeneous data sources using an XML
            formalism. It
            intends to offer a simple unified way to access, modify, transform and generate XML streams from XML
            datasources or
            relational DB. XGQL is available in several modes. One of them is the SWAS <a
                href="https://sourceforge.net/item/showfiles.php?group_id=154418">SWAS</a>. It consists in a Jetty
            Server
            running the XGQL servlet.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://docs.xp-dev.com/
        </link>
        <image>xpdev.png
        </image>
        <title>XP-Dev</title>
        <description>
            XP-Dev.com provides free and commercial Subversion Hosting integrated with item Tracking for all types of
            items - open and even closed source items.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.xpolog.com
        </link>
        <image>xpologo.gif
        </image>
        <title>XPO Log</title>
        <description>
            XpoLog is a debug server. Enable data view and analysis over any log and configuration file. You can tail
            view
            changing files, transform the files to a table, and customize it. Merge a number of log files for multitier
            system
            debugging. Filter the data by a variety of rules. Zip and export files by e-mail or as a plain text. One
            server can
            be configured to reference many files on different machines.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.z2-environment.eu/
        </link>
        <image>z2.png
        </image>
        <title>Z2-Environment</title>
        <description>
            The z2-Environment is an infrastructure to develop, configure, and run standard Java solutions requiring no
            build
            infrastructure nor deployment procedures. Z2 greatly simplifies team development, support as well as
            distributed
            operations of Java solutions. The z2-Environment uses Jetty as its Web Container.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.zedbuildsandbugs.com/
        </link>
        <image>hericus-logo.png
        </image>
        <title>Zed Builds and Bugs</title>
        <description>
            Zed Builds And Bugs Manager integrates 4 common development tools: continuous integration builds, bug
            tracking,
            discussion forums, and wiki collaboration into a single easy to use web application. It is free for small
            development teams, and ready to scale to the requirements of your item.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <link>https://www.zimbra.com/products/desktop.html
        </link>
        <image>zimbra_desktop.gif
        </image>
        <title>Zimbra Desktop</title>
        <description>
            Zimbra Desktop is the next generation leap forward for Web 2.0 applications- now you can have Zimbra's
            Ajax-based
            collaboration experience online and offline. That means when you are out of the office without a connection
            (say, in
            a plane, train, or automobile), you can keep working without missing a beat. Write email, add new
            appointments, edit
            documents and when you re-connect changes will be automatically synced to the Zimbra Server.
        </description>
    </item>
</items>